<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<framexml>
<data>

<!-- 1M2 -->
<text><![CDATA[<B>Our past</B>]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <b>Indus Valley Civilization</b> developed around the plains of the River Indus in about 2600<FONT SIZE="15" font face="Comic Sans MS">BCE</FONT>.]]></text>

<text><![CDATA[<b>Harappa</b> and <b>Mohenjo Daro</b> are two of the most famous archaeological sites of the Indus Valley Civilization.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Archaeologists have found pieces of pottery, jewellery, clay figures, and seals at Harappa and Mohenjo Daro.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Seals with inscriptions]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <b>Aryans</b> came to the subcontinent from Central Asia around 1500<FONT SIZE="15" font face="Comic Sans MS">BCE</FONT>]]></text>

<text><![CDATA[The Aryans brought a new culture to the subcontinent. They also brought a new language, Sanskrit, and a religion called <I>Hinduism</I> with them.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <b>Persians</b> came into the subcontinent during the 5<font face="GG Superscript">th</font> century    Their capital here was Taxila.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Greeks under Alexander the Great defeated the Persians and crossed into the subcontinent through the Khyber Pass.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Greeks influenced the art and sculpture in Gandhara and Taxila.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <b>Mauryans</b> and the <b>Kushans</b> came to power after the Persians were defeated by the Greeks.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[<b>Ashoka</b> was the most famous Mauryan ruler.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[<b>Kanishka</b> was the most famous Kushan ruler.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Mauryans and the Kushans were followed by the <b>Gupta</b> dynasty.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Guptas built a large and powerful empire under <b>Chandra Gupta</b>.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Parthians and the Huns came into the subcontinent from the north-west.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[<b>Harsha</b>, the ruler of the <b>Nanda</b> dynasty, set up the Nalanda University.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Most of the early people in this region were <b>Hindus</b> and <b>Buddhists</b>. Jainism also spread within India.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[<b>Islam</b> spread in the subcontinent with the arrival of <b>Mohammad bin Qasim</b> in the 8<font face="GG Superscript">th</font> century]]></text>








<!-- Caption -->
<text><![CDATA[Mohenjo Daro]]></text>s
<text><![CDATA[Harappa]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Aryans]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Persians]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Taxila]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Gandhara]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Ashoka's edict pillar]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Coins from the Kushan period]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[harsha]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Nalanda University ruins]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Mohammad bin Qasim]]></text>
<asd><![CDATA[Coins from the Gupta period]]></asd>









</data>
</framexml>