<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<framexml>
<data>

<!-- 1M2 -->
<text><![CDATA[<B>The government</B>]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Pakistan became an independent country on 14 August 1947.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Pakistan became a democratic country. The democracy is based on the ideals of Islam.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In a democracy, people elect leaders to rule the country.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Elections are held every 5 years and people above 18 years of age can vote.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Through voting, people elect members of the <B>national</B> and <B>provincial assemblies</B>.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The members of the national and provincial assemblies elect the members of the <B>Senate</B>, which is the upper house.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <I>prime minister</I> is the head of the government.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <I>chief minister</I> is the head of a province. The chief minister appoints his own ministers.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The National Assembly Building]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Work of the government]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Tax]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Budget]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[A <I>constitution</I> is a set of rules which everyone in the country must follow.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[A constitution helps the people of a country to stop any party from staying in power all the time or making their own laws.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <I>president</I> is the head of the state. His duty is to see that the country is being run in accordance with the rules of the constitution.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Each province is headed by a governor who makes sure that the provincial assembly is also following the rules of the constitution.]]></text>

<!-- Caption -->
<text><![CDATA[Important matters such as laws for the whole country are debated in the National Assembly.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The President's House]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Governor's House in Quetta]]></text>
<asd><![CDATA[The Prime Minister's Secretariat]]></asd>



</data>
</framexml>