<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<framexml>
<data>

<!-- 1M2 -->
<text><![CDATA[<B>The Western Highlands</B>]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The <B>Western Highlands</B> are situated in the north and west of our country.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[These extend from the Makran Coast in the south to the extreme northern mountainous region.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Himalayas]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Siwaliks or Sub-Himalayas is the southernmost range of the Himalayas.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Beyond the Siwaliks, lies the Lesser Himalayas which are higher than the Siwaliks.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Great Himalayas form the highest part of the North.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Karakoram mountains]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The average height of the Karakoram mountains is 6100 metres.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Mount Godwin Austen (K2), the second highest peak of the world, lies in the Karakoram Range. It is 8611 metres high.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Karakoram Highway connects Pakistan to China.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Hindu Kush mountains]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Balochistan Plateau lies to the west of the Sulaiman and Kirthar ranges.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Potohar Plateau lies between the Jhelum and Indus rivers. ]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Indus River]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[It is about 2900 kilometres long.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The source of the Indus is near Lake Mansorawar in Tibet.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The plains formed by the River Indus provide Pakistan with its best agricultural land.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The rivers Jhelum, Chenab, Ravi, and Sutlej join together at Panjnad and then join the Indus at Mithankot.]]></text>
			   

<!-- Caption -->
<text><![CDATA[Makran Coast]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Northern mountains]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Siwaliks]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Rawalpindi]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Lesser Himalayas]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Murree]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Ghoragali]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Great Himalayas]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Nanga Parbat]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Mount Godwin Austen]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Karakoram Highway]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Tirich Mir (7690 metres)]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Noshaq (7484 metres)]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Kohistan]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Swat]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Dir]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Balochistan Plateau]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Potohar plateau]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Indus River]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Mansorawar Lake]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Canal]]></text>

<text><![CDATA[The Karakoram mountains form the extreme northern boundary of Pakistan.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Hindu Kush mountains form the north and north-western borders of Pakistan.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Kohistan, Swat, and Dir ranges lie to the south of the Hindu Kush range.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Indus is the most important river in Pakistan.]]></text>

<option><![CDATA[Nanga Parbat]]></option>
<option><![CDATA[<b>River Indus and its plains</b>]]></option>


</data>
</framexml>