<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<framexml>
<data>

<!-- 1M2 -->
<text><![CDATA[<B>Religion and languages</B>]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Culture of a country]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Our country is called the <b>Islamic Republic of Pakistan</b> as nearly 96% of the population are Muslims.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Hazrat Muhammad <FONT SIZE="16" COLOR="">(PBUH)</FONT> was the last messenger of Allah to whom the Holy Quran was revealed.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The followers of Islam are called Muslims. Muslims believe in only one God called Allah.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Muslims also believe that those who do good for others will be rewarded when they die with an afterlife in Paradise. ]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Hinduism is one of the oldest religions in the world.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Bhagavad Gita is one of the holy books of the Hindus.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Christians are people who follow the teachings of the prophet Jesus Christ.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Bible is the holy book of the Christians.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Sikhism is a religion preached by a saint called Guru Nanak.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The holy book of the Sikhs is the Guru Granth Sahib.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Gautama Buddha was the founder of Buddhism.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[He became known as the Buddha or the Enlightened One.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Parsees follow the teachings of their prophet Zoroaster.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The holy book of the Parsees is called the Avesta.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Urdu is the national language of Pakistan.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Punjabi, Pashto, Sindhi, Balochi, and Gujrati are some other languages spoken in Pakistan.]]></text>




<!-- Caption -->
<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Religions]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Languages]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Science]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Foods]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Literature]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Architecture]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Painting]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Music]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Dance]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Handicrafts]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Prophet Zoroaster]]></text>




</data>
</framexml>