<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<framexml>
<data>

<!-- 1M2 -->
<text><![CDATA[<B>Power, minerals, and industries </B>]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[An industrial country produces goods using its own power and natural resources.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[To develop industrially, any country requires power, water supply, raw materials, machines, and workers.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Hydroelectricity is generated from water stored in dams across rivers.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The power generated by burning coal, gas or oil is called <I>thermal power</I>.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[a thermal power plant]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Power can also be generated by constructing nuclear or atomic power plants.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Solar power is generated by using the energy of the Sun.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Wind power is generated from wind by setting up windmills.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Power generated from cow dung is called <I>biogas</I>.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Power is also generated by extracting ethanol from sugar cane and maize.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[A steady supply of water is necessary for industries as water is used in many parts of the production process.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Any matter in its natural state which is not man-made is a <I>raw material</I>.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Minerals are essential for industries.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Metallic minerals]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Non-metallic minerals]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Oil, coal, and natural gas are called <I>fossil fuels</I>.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Iron and steel, engineering, fertilizers, chemicals, cement, and textiles are some of the major industries in Pakistan.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Small industries that produce goods such as furniture, handicrafts, embroidery, and carpets are called <I>cottage industries</I>.]]></text>






<!-- Caption -->
<text><![CDATA[Dam]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Thermal power production]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Nuclear power plant]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Solar panels to produce solar power]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Windmills]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Biogas plant]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Ethanol plant]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Iron ore]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Wood]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Iron ore]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Copper]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Gold]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Rock salt]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Emerald ]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Ruby ]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Fossil fuels are formed from animal or plant remains buried deep underground for millions of years.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Cottage industry]]></text>



</data>
</framexml>