<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<framexml>
<data>

<!-- 1M2 -->
<text><![CDATA[<B>Muslim rule in the subcontinent</B>]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Prophet Muhammad <FONT SIZE="16" COLOR="">(PBUH)</FONT> was born in 570 <FONT SIZE="16" COLOR="">CE</FONT> in Makkah.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[He received his first divine message from Allah in 610 and so declared the religion of Islam.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[After Hazrat Muhammad <FONT SIZE="16" COLOR="">(PBUH)</FONT> passed away in 632, Islam spread from Arabia to other parts of Africa, Asia, and Europe.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In 712, Mohammad bin Qasim defeated Raja Dahir of Sindh and conquered the lands from the Arabian Sea coast up to Multan.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Mohammad bin Qasim established a strong and just government with good reforms for the people.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Due to these reforms, many people willingly converted to Islam.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[By the end of the 11<FONT FACE="GG Superscript">th</FONT> century, Muslim rule was firmly established in the region that is now Pakistan.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The ruler of Ghazni, Mahmud, was among the early Muslim invaders from the north-west.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In 1192, the Afghan ruler, Mohammad Ghori conquered all of northern India up to Bengal.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Qutbuddin Aibak formed the Delhi Sultanate in 1206.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Khaljis came to power and ruled from 1290 to 1320.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Ibn Batuta, the famous Arab traveller, lived at the court of Muhammad Tughlaq.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Tughlaqs were followed by the Sayyids.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Sayyids were followed by the Lodhis.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In 1398, Timur, the Mongol warlord, attacked and destroyed Delhi.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In 1526, Babur, the king of Kabul, defeated Ibrahim Lodhi and founded the Mughal Empire in the subcontinent.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Babur was succeeded by his son Humayun.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Humayun was defeated by the Afghan general Sher Shah Suri in 1540.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Humayun recovered his kingdom after the death of Sher Shah Suri.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Akbar was the greatest of all the Mughal kings who expanded the Mughal Empire. He ruled from 1556 to 1605.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Akbar was succeeded by Jahangir who ruled from 1605 to 1627.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Shah Jahan, the successor of Jahangir, built the world famous Taj Mahal in Agra.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Shah Jahan was succeeded by Aurangzeb who extended the Mughal Empire to its largest limit.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Due to Aurangzeb's constant war with the Marathas and the Rajputs, the Mughal Empire weakened.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The Mughal kings did much for the subcontinent.]]></text>

<!-- Caption -->
<text><![CDATA[Sultan Mahmud]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Mohammad Ghori]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Qutbuddin Aibak]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Balban]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Alauddin Khalji]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Muhammad Tughlaq]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Ibn Batuta]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Babur]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Humayun]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Sher Shah Suri]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Akbar]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Jahangir ]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Shah Jahan]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Aurangzeb]]></text>




</data>
</framexml> 