<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<framexml>
<data>

<!-- 1M2 -->
<text><![CDATA[<B>The soil and agriculture</B>]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[The agriculture of a country depends on the kind of soil and rocks that are found there.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Agriculture is possible only in those places where there is fertile soil and enough water.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In mountainous regions, agriculture is not possible as there is snow on the ground for most of the year and the land is rocky.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In the river valleys between mountains and in the river plains, the soil is usually fertile.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[People settle in these valleys and plains to practise agriculture.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Deserts are sandy and water is scarce, so it is difficult to grow crops.]]></text>


<text><![CDATA[By building canals, desert areas can also be made fertile.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Alluvial soil is the most fertile soil. It is found in the plains around rivers.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Fast flowing rivers in the mountains break up the rocks and cut through the earth. This is called <I>erosion</I>.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Soil loses fertility during heavy showers as the fast-flowing water carries away much of the soil at the surface and exposes the rocks beneath.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Planting trees helps to protect the topsoil as the roots hold soil particles together.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Punjab and Sindh are the major agricultural regions of Pakistan.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Punjab and Sindh have the largest network of canals which helps in irrigation.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[In mountainous regions, farmers practise terrace farming by making fields on the mountain slopes.]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[]]></text>

<!-- Caption -->
<text><![CDATA[River erosion]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Canal]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Terrace farming]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[cotton]]></text>      
<text><![CDATA[sugar cane]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[tobacco]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[jute]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[wheat]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[rice]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[maize]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[millet]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Livestock farming]]></text>
<text><![CDATA[Poultry farm]]></text>
</data>
</framexml>